<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on </title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:39:54 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trees</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:39:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/trees/</guid>
      <description>trees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:34:25 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/test/</guid>
      <description>a;lkj;lkj;lkj</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the souflaki dimension</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/the-souflaki-dimension/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 22:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/the-souflaki-dimension/</guid>
      <description>In Chicago I rode an airport bus on a suprisingly long journey, on that road system in the city within the city that is O&amp;rsquo;hare. Trash was blowing in the grey wind, but not homeless people. It was just me and two caffeinated and nicotein-ed flight attendents, on their endless journey around the world in metal tubes. At the gate there was a babel of yiddish, the anguish of young children, and other unknown exotic noises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Log From the Sea of Cortez</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/another-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 14:29:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/another-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez/</guid>
      <description>Its a nice one&#xA;Biking down the coast south of La Paz I knew a wonderful freedom sleeping on the sand and going snorkelling whenever nessecary to cool off, which was quite often. Once I got a little scared snorkelling alone in deep water with a steep rocky coast, and stinging jellyfish going under my shirt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the other la paz</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/the-other-la-paz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 22:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/the-other-la-paz/</guid>
      <description>Coming out of the mountains. Very steep. Roads along the coast plunge straight into the sea. Running out of food, but when try to buy, fisherman just give us tacos and rum. It is difficult to make many km when people constantly ply you with tacos.&#xA;Many drunk people must have died here.&#xA;mysterious Jesus cave. Although we were there on easter unfortunately there was no ressurections&#xA;Huge canyons in the Sierra de Gigante.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ranchos</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/ranchos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 22:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/ranchos/</guid>
      <description>Time blurs, dates become meaningless. Days become puncated by invitations for tacos, beers, cafes, building fires morning and night. If lucky there is sometimes a fog, called a &amp;ldquo;brisa&amp;rdquo; (in other parts brisa means breeze, so it can be confusing) . But usually there is only that short wonderful period when the sun has not creeped over the hill again, that you are not roasting by the sun. A nice time in the tropics, when the birds come alive, a goat bellows in the distance, and the air is so cool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>queque</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/queque/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 22:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/queque/</guid>
      <description>One morning I saw a guy picking up garbage in the middle of nada. That&amp;rsquo;s not something you see everyday in Mexico. He was a troquero, owned a trucking business with his brother. They ran out of hydraulic fluid so his brother had to drive to the nearest town to find some. He was picking up botes (cans) to redeem for scrap while he waited. Luckily there was no shortage as the most popular pastime is downing tecates and throwing the bote out the window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No abre la boca o entran las moscas</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/no-abre-la-boca-o-entran-las-moscas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 22:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/no-abre-la-boca-o-entran-las-moscas/</guid>
      <description>In Bahía, a California weed farmer who&amp;rsquo;s mothers&amp;rsquo; family was from my hometown, and two brothers of someone I went to high school with, also from my hometown. Seemingly crazy odds like this seem to happen quite often.&#xA;Stories about cartels, corrupt police. Neighbors dissapearing in the night. Drug running accross the Sea of Cortez from Sinaloa. They have a saying, &amp;ldquo;No abre la bica o entran las moscas&amp;rdquo; (Don&amp;rsquo;t open your mouth or the flies will come in).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>abalones</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/abalones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 16:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/abalones/</guid>
      <description>Abalones, longosta. Here they are both sold almost exclusively to Chinese buyers. The abalone are harvested by a man in a wetsuit, breathing from a hose going to the surface.&#xA;fried abalones&#xA;dried lobster, if only I had unlimited supply&#xA;Omar and Tere feed us, put us up in a shack, tellmany stories of the world passing by the village of just a few families. Cyclists, motos, someone running down mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tripa&#39;s Revenge</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/tripas-revenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 21:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/tripas-revenge/</guid>
      <description>In Vicente Guererro I only briefly enjoyed a tripe taco. Several hours after I ate it it wanted to escape my belly. Luckily thete was an old coffee can by my tent, as it took several hours for that taco to finally escape.&#xA;this tumbleweed could take out a cyclist&#xA;Beautiful estuary&#xA;Marie, owner of Super Torta la Unica and her son Ramses, who rented us a room for a few nights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyclist Resources</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/cyclist-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 18:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/cyclist-resources/</guid>
      <description>Get a bicycle. You will not regret it. If you live. -Mark Twain&#xA;Some useful resources and links for cycle touring.&#xA;Hospitality networks trustroots.org - slowly gaining traction https://welcometomygarden.org/ -slow travellers, no cars! warmshowers.org the old main cycling network, see below couchsurfing.com -see below Heberge un Cyclo Voyageur Couchers - new alternative to couchsurfing BeWelcome - quite big, mainly europe? casa de ciclistas (see section) The main hospex (hospitality exchange) networks of the past, couchsurfing and warmshowers, have sadly fallen under more and more corporate sway that is not nessecarily aligned with the interests of the people in them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chorros</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/chorros/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 03:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/chorros/</guid>
      <description>Arriving at the coast I am greeted by a man named Yiyo and his wife. They are collecting chorros (mussels) and fishing, having been married just a few days before.&#xA;It turns out they run a famous seafood restaurant in Ensanada. Soon I am being plied with beer and amazing feast of chorros and tacos de camarones. All cooked on offcuts from the fender guitar factory in Ensanada. Yiyo takes me fishing, scrambling over cliffs trying to avoid pacific swells crashing in, casting out for lingcod.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quesadillas</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/quesadillas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 02:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/quesadillas/</guid>
      <description>Tecate had some cool rocks, looked like cataviña further South.&#xA;nice trails leaving tecate&#xA;I made a very bold decision and sent my stove ahead to a warmshowers host in La Paz, as I had heard the thing to do was grill on the fire every night. So armed with an old toaster oven rack and some beans and tortillas I set off.&#xA;First night en ruta it already paid off with quesadillas and roasted peppers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontera</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/frontera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 17:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/frontera/</guid>
      <description>San Diego, a city of noisy concrete freeways and some nice people. After some days of rain the sun shone so I embarked south.&#xA;along the san diego river&#xA;In chula vista I met a guy Steve who had a car hit his tandem bike in Florida, he spent months in the hospital and still couldn&amp;rsquo;t walk much. And then after the accident somebody stole the bike.&#xA;Camped in peak above otay in the dark above thle lights of Tijuana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fox Fit Damper Oil Change</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/fox-fit-damper-oil-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 12:24:50 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/fox-fit-damper-oil-change/</guid>
      <description>After five years or so the fit4 cartridge damper in my 2017 fox34 (id C8sb) was quite sluggish. This is to be expected as the bladder ingests oil over time.&#xA;The damper cartridge is easy to remove with a socket or just a large adjustable wrench. The tricky part is removing the valve at the top in order to drain the old oil and refill. I was following the official fox fit4 damper guide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:15:35 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>You can contact me with passenger pigeon, smoke signals, or&#xA;If you want to get an email when a new post is published, then send an email to the above address with the word &amp;ldquo;subscribe&amp;rdquo; in the subject.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/markdown-syntax-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href=&#34;https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&#34;&gt;https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WELCOME BACK</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 21:54:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Hello to all my dieheart fans (my mother). I&amp;rsquo;m happy to report that I&amp;rsquo;m still alive for now (against many odds). Don&amp;rsquo;t hold your breath but its possible this blog could expand in the coming decades. For now I leave you with a baby llama I had the pleasure of meeting recently. An unpleasant creature that tried to attack me multiple times, and chased me out of the village.&#xA;king of las papas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/20200714152828-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/20200714152828-books/</guid>
      <description>&lt;?xml version=&#34;1.0&#34; encoding=&#34;utf-8&#34;?&gt; &lt;!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC &#34;-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Strict//EN&#34; &#34;http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-strict.dtd&#34;&gt; Once is Enough Once is Enough Beryl and Miles Smeeton, apparently legends. In their chinese junk? the Tzu Hang and with their daughter. info article info from daughter of man who built boat Nice overview of the Smeetons-from the book &amp;rsquo;The Circumnavigators&amp;rsquo; by Don Holm 16mm film from Guzzwell!! from here From Victoria Harbour History: &amp;ldquo;In 1969 the Smeetons sold Tzu Hang to thier friend, Bob Nance, and moved to Alberta to found the Cochrane Ecological Institute dedicated to breeding endangered wildlife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/googleb3a3f539ef90357d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/googleb3a3f539ef90357d/</guid>
      <description>google-site-verification: googleb3a3f539ef90357d.html&#xA;&#xA;a;dslkfja;lkdsjf</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/notes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;?xml version=&#34;1.0&#34; encoding=&#34;utf-8&#34;?&gt; &lt;!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC &#34;-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Strict//EN&#34; &#34;http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-strict.dtd&#34;&gt; overstaying shengen overstaying shengen Table of Contents 1. portugol specifically: https://old.reddit.com/r/travel/comments/qalolt/has_anyone_used_usaeu_bilateral_visa_agreements/ihu078l/?context=3 1.1. new law extending expired visas until end of 2023! 2. spain 3. italy 4. france 5. nordic bloc, norway and sweden, denmark https://www.tripadvisor.com.ph/ShowTopic-g190455-i550-k10843270-Do_You_Travel_Bilaterally_Bilateral_Visa_Agreements-Norway.html 5.1. denmark specifically 6. overstaying penalties 7. TODO contact embassies. 8. being asked for proof at border when using bilateral agreement 8.1. TODO https://old.reddit.com/r/solotravel/comments/xw9g2l/new_and_updated_guide_to_legally_stay_180_days_in/jg9gk74/p official bilateral visa agreements (EU government) https://old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/tents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/tents/</guid>
      <description>&lt;?xml version=&#34;1.0&#34; encoding=&#34;utf-8&#34;?&gt; &lt;!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC &#34;-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Strict//EN&#34; &#34;http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-strict.dtd&#34;&gt; tents tents Table of Contents 1. xmid 1.1. high wind https://www.trek-lite.com/index.php?threads/dan-durston-massdrop-x-mid.4960/post-225868 1.2. reports in high winds 1.3. guyline failure 1.4. picture showing mid panel guyouts 1.5. xmid vs betalite 2. poles 2.0.1. using v-poles to make a-frame inside mid shelter 3. stakes 3.1. dac j-stake 4. rewaterproofing tents 5. strange moss tent convention 6. 1907 abercrombie and fitch catalog 7.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
